Thank you for watching!
I don't know what you're thinking.
I'm not going to let them get in the way of my emotions
Alone, I'll only dream till morning
Even in my dreams, it's you
My heart is a disgrace
I can't let my feelings take over
I can't say goodbye
Soon we'll be together and no one will need us
Such is the nature of this love
We'll be together soon
Palm of my hand, the scarred remnant
I'll never give up on this love
Though it won't be abandoned
With a straight heart
Morning is coming
I want to tell you
Shout, even if my voice is dead and it won't come out
Shout, somehow I have to deliver it to you
Don't run away, your earnest gaze's answer will continue
Shout, for the first time I have this feeling
Shout, I don't know how to handle it
What a lot more words there are
I love you, I'm anxious, I'm sure it's you, I'm sure it's you
Now this summer love
I'll come back to the place of my heart's pounding
I don't even have the heart to make it
I don't need it, I just want to say so
I've believed in you for a long time
I won't lie about how I feel
The sky will turn to summer
It's the first time I've ever felt the urge to remember.
Even the urge to remember.
I can't stop thinking about you. I can't stop thinking about you.
I've always loved you.
The moment we meet
Love begins
Thank you very much for coming to Transmitch.
Thank you very much.
Did you have a good time?
Yes!
Did it seem like you would come back?
Please keep in touch with Motto Echo Albee.
That's all for now, Motto Echo Albee.
Thank you very much.
First day is over.
Fukuoka Love Chu!
Momochan's impression was really neat,
I really have to get it right or I'll be 20 years old!
I'm 20 years old too.
I'm also 20 years old,
I want to be able to give smart feedback,
That's my goal for this tour.
Mental course!
Last!
Two pieces!
Yay!
Last!
Okay, thank you!
Thank you!
Take it!
What?
What what?
Okay!
Hey!
Hey! That's what I'm talking about,
Not Equal Me National Tour 2023
The first day of WISH OUT!
I just said it was the first day, but I did it normally.
Yes! So, last time, you know,
Fukuoka, where I was able to come for the finals.
I was so happy to be able to come to Fukuoka on the first day,
This time, we released our 6th single and toured there,
And since this was the tour after the release of the 6th single, we performed the coupling song for the first time, and so on,
I was very happy that everyone could see our coupling song for the first time and the title song.
What is the schedule for this national tour of Noimee?
This national tour of Noimee started from Fukuoka,Starting here in Fukuoka,
I will be touring all over Japan.
Finally, I will be standing on the stage of my dreams, the Nippon Budokan,
The time has come for us to start accepting applications.
We are also preparing for the event, imagining the smiles on everyone's faces as they enjoy themselves,
We are preparing for the event with our best efforts, imagining everyone's smiling faces as they enjoy the show,
We are looking forward to spending time with many of you.
Noimy-chan is still getting better and better, so please keep your eyes on her,
Please keep your eyes on her.
So, thank you very much for your time.
I look forward to seeing you all at the venue.
Mr. Crab was also there.